(lively synth pop)
♪ I've been there, done
that, messed around ♪
♪ I'm having fun ♪
♪ Don't put me down ♪
♪ I'll never let you
sweep me off my feet ♪
♪ And I won't let you in again ♪
♪ The messages I've tried to send ♪
♪ My information's just not going in ♪
♪ I'm burning bridges shore to shore ♪
♪ I break away from something more ♪
♪ I'm not turned on to
love until it's cheap ♪
♪ I've been there, done
that, messed around ♪
♪ I'm having fun, don't put me down ♪
♪ I'll never let you
sweep me off my feet ♪
♪ This time, baby, I'll be bulletproof ♪
(lively synth pop)
♪ I won't let you turn
around ♪ ♪ And tell me now ♪
♪ I'm much too proud ♪
♪ To walk away from
something when it's dead ♪
♪ Do, do, do your dirty words ♪
♪ Come out to play when you are hurt ♪
♪ There's certain things
that should be left unsaid ♪
♪ Tick, tick, tick, tick on the watch ♪
♪ And life's too short for me to stop ♪
♪ Oh baby, your time is running out ♪
♪ I won't let you turn around ♪
♪ And tell me now I'm much too proud ♪
♪ All you do is fill me up with doubt ♪
♪ This time, baby, I'll be bulletproof ♪
♪ This time ♪
♪ I'll be ♪
♪ Bulletproof ♪
♪ This time ♪
♪ I'll be ♪
♪ Bulletproof ♪
(upbeat synth pop)
♪ This time, baby, I'll be bulletproof ♪
(upbeat percussive music)